A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1976-1985.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files, 1978-1982 (Accession 33039)., Extent: 20 cubic feet (20 boxes)
  - Comptroller, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Comptroller - Financial reporting, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Computer Services, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Elections, State Board of, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 12)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 12)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Division of Administration, 1982. (Box 12)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Consolidated Laboratory, 1982-1983. (Box 12)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Risk Management, 1982-1983. (Box 12)
  - Treasury, Dept. of the, 1982-1983. (Box 13)
  - Treasury Board, 1982. (Box 13)
  - Legislation, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Legislation - Budget bill, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Legislative coordination, 1982-1983. (Box 13)
  - Legislative impact statements, 1982-1983. (Box 13)
  - Lindley, James T., 1981. (Box 13)
  - Memos to all state agencies and institutions, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Memos to Admininstration and Finance agencies, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - General, 1978. (Box 14a)
  - Correspondence - Office of Education, 1978. (Box 14a)
  - Correspondence - Human Resources, 1978. (Box 14a)
  - Correspondence - Public Safety, 1978. (Box 14a)
  - Correspondence - Transportation, 19. (Box 14a)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Secretaries, 1976-1978. (Box 14a)
  - Cabinet - Description of duties, 1974-1978. (Box 14a)
  - Cabinet - Information Committee, 1974-1978. (Box 14a)
  - Position papers from C. B. Walker, 1978. (Box 14a)
  - Speeches - M. B. Rowe, 1976-1978. (Box 14a)
  - Speeches - M. B. Rowe, 1972-1976. (Box 14a)
  - Richmond Kiwanis Club, 1976-1979. (Box 14a)
  - Energy Project (Saltville), 1978. (Box 14b)
  - Emergency Management of Resources, 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Energy Conservation Program, 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Space requirements, 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Employment forms, undated. (Box 14b)
  - Federal property on loan, 1977-1979. (Box 14b)
  - Federal excess property forms, 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Advisory Committees - Annual reports, 1978. (Box 14b)
  - Property recommendations for 1978 - Report of the Commission on State Governmental Management, 1978. (Box 14b)
  - Appendices to Proposals for Coastal Resources Management in Virginia - Draft (Secretary of Commerce and Resources), 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Alternatives for Coastal Resources Management in Virginia - Draft (Secretary of Commerce and Resources), 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Annual Meeting of State Employees' Credit Union, 1978. (Box 14b)
  - Governor's Management Study - A Report on Implementation, 1973. (Box 14b)
  - Memos - Dept. of Planning and Budget, Personnel, Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Council on the Environment, 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Appropriation request (1978-1980 Biennium), 1977. (Box 14b)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Municipal League, Virginia, 1983. (Box 15)
  - National Governors Association, 1983. (Box 15)
  - National Academy of Public Administration, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Office of Management and Budget Bulletins, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Press Releases, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Savings Bond Campaign, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Senate Finance Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 15)
  - Sheriff's Association, Virginia State, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Space Radiation Effects Laboratory, 1981. (Box 15)
  - Speeches - Governor, 1983. (Box 15)
  - State Governments, Council of, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Tax and spending limits, 1979-1980. (Box 15)
  - Taxation issue papers, undated. (Box 15)
  - Transitional Center for Emotionally Disturbed Deaf Adults, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Vendors, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 Jan. (Box 16)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 Feb. (Box 16)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 Mar. (Box 16)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 Apr. (Box 16)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 May. (Box 16)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 June. (Box 16)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 July. (Box 16)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 Aug. (Box 16)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1982 Sept. (Box 16)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Telecommunications, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Treasury Board, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Treasury, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Retirement System (VSRS), 1983. (Box 17)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernment Affairs, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Administration and Finance - Financial statements, 1982-1983. (Box 17)
  - Administration and Finance - Directives, 1980-1982. (Box 17)
  - Affirmative Action Reports by agencies, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1983. (Box 18)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1984 Jan. (Box 19)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1984 Feb. (Box 19)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1984 Mar. (Box 19)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1984 Apr. (Box 19)
  - General Services - Engineering and Buildings, 1982-1983. (Box 20)
  - General Services - Purchases and Supply, 1983. (Box 20)
  - Local Government, Commission on, 1983. (Box 20)
  - Managment Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 20)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 20)
  - State Internal Auditor, Office of the, 1983. (Box 20)
- Correspondence and subject files, 1974-1985 (Accession 37778)., Extent: x cubic feet (x boxes)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Dept. of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Highways and Transportation, Dept. of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Housing, Office of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Housing Development Authority, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Housing and Urban Development Authority, Dept. of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Industrial Development, Division of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Institute of Marine Science, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Division of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Labor, Virginia Dept. of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Legislative Tracking System, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Library, Virginia State, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Memos to Maurice B. Rowe from Richard H. Kirby, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Personnel, Division of (Memos to Agency Heads), 1974. (Box 1)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, Division of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, Division of - Advisory Committee, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Planning Districts, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Port Authority, Virginia, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Privacy and Security of State Information, Study of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Professional and Occupational Regulation, Dept. of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Property and Records, Division of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Republican Governor's Administration, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Revenue Sharing, Federal, 1974. (Box 1)
  - S.S. United State Study, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Science and Technology in State Government, 1974. (Box 1)
  - State Building Code Review, 1974. (Box 1)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Virginia Manpower Planning Council, 1974. (Box 1)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Agriculture and Commerce, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Amendments to Appropriations Act by General Assembly, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Art Commission, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Atlantic Rural Exposition - State Fair exhibit, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Attorney General, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Automated Data Processing, Division of (#1), 1975. (Box 2)
  - Automated Data Processing, Division of (#2), 1975. (Box 2)
  - Bills signed by the Governor, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Bills and Resolutions of the General Assembly, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Budget, Division of the, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Budget Hearings - Governor's Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Budget form 27-T, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budget - Office of Administration, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budget - 1974-1976 Biennium, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budget forms approved, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budget - Office of Commerce and Resources, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budget - Dept. of Corrections, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budget - Office of Education, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budget - Office of Finance, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budgetary Management Process, 1975. (Box 3)
  - Budget - Joint House Appropriations and Senate Finance Committee meeting, 1975 Nov. (Box 3)
  - Budget Office of Human Resources, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Budget - Office of Public Safety, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Energy, Virgina Office of, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Energy - Cheatham Annex, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Central Garage - Car Pool Committee, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Coastal Plains Regional Commission, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Code Commission, Virginia, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Community Action Programs, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Community Colleges, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Compensation Board, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Comptroller, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Consultant firms, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Consumer Affairs, 1975. (Box 4)
  - Corrections, Dept. of (#1), 1975. (Box 4)
  - Corrections, Dept. of (#2), 1975. (Box 4)
  - Correctional Institutions - Overcrowding, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Council of State Governments, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Council on the Environment, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Crime Commission, Virginia, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Economic Development, Office of, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Economic Opportunity Act, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Economics in State Government, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Education Assistance Authority, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Education Commission of the States, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Education Loan Authority, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Electricity Costs Commission, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Emergency Services, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Emergency Job Program, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Engineering and Buildings, Division of, 1975. (Box 5)
  - Managers in State Government, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development (MASD), 1978. (Box 6)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development (MASD) - Breifing, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development (MASD) - Reports, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Memoranda - All agency heads, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Memoranda - Administration and Finance agency heads, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Memoranda - Cabinet, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Metric System, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Miller, Ronald W., 1978. (Box 6)
  - Model General Assembly, 1978. (Box 6)
  - National Governors Association, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Peat, Marwick and Mitchell Co., 1978. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Responses to general correspondence, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Employee position control, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Personnel Authority, State, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Personnel Management Advisory Committee, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Merit system, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Reports, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Salary surveys / scales, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Vacancies, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Public Records Advisory Committee, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Purchase and Supply, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Purchase and Supply, Dept. of - Printing, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Purchase and Supply, Dept. of - Surplus property, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Retirement System, Virginia Supplemental, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Retirement System, Virginia Supplemental - Audit files/reports, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Retirement System, Virginia Supplemental - Correspondence, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Retirement System, Virginia Supplemental - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Revenue Sharing, U.S. Office, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Revenue Resources and Economic Commission, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Revenue estimates, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Resources Information System, Virginia, 1978. (Box 7)
  - Legislative Tracking System, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Minority Business Enterprise, Office of, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Memos to Rowe from Kirby, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Metric System, 1975. (Box 8)
  - National Federation of Independent Businesses, 1975. (Box 8)
  - National Governors Association, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Management and Budget, Office of, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, 1975. (Box 8)
  - PMIS Management Review Board, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Parking Task Force, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Memos to agencies, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Personnel class specifications, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Photocopying costs, 1975. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, Division of State, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, Division of State - Reports, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Planning districts, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Planning Ad Hoc Committee, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Privacy and security information, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Probation and Parole Board, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Port Authority, Virginia, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Purchases and Supply, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Register Commission, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Revenue Sharing, Office of, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Schools, Fran, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Science Museum of Virginia, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth - Appointments, 1975. (Box 9)
  - Special Programs, Office of, 1975. (Box 10)
  - S.S. United States, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Southern Governor's Association, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1975. (Box 10)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1975. (Box 10)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1975. (Box 10)
  - State owned property, 1975. (Box 10)
  - State organization and membership information, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Supplemental Retirement System, Virginia, 1975. (Box 10)
  - State Stationary, Official, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Treasury, Virginia Dept. of the, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Volunteerism, Office of, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation, Virginia, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Virginia Public Telecommunications Council, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1975. (Box 10)
  - VEPCO negotiations, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Virginia Criminal Information Network, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Business Reports, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Public Buildings Commission, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Welfare, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Weston, Portie (Mrs.), 1975. (Box 11)
  - Water Control Board, 1975. (Box 10)
  - Cabinet expdenitures, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Cabinet Information Committee, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Cabinet reorganization, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Cabinet Printing Committee, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Cabinet Mail and Message Committee, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Memos to Cabinet, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Education, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Human Affairs, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Cabinet Deputy Assistant, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Administration, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1975. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Finance, 1972-1973. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Finance - Meeting summary, 1973. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Finance - Memos, 1972-1973. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Finance - Mission, 1972. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Finance - Priorities, 1972. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Finance - Reports from Agencies / Governor's Year End News Conference, 1972. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Finance - Organization chart, 1972. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Finance - Outdoor Recreation, Commission of, 1973. (Box 11)
  - Energy Resource Advisory Commission, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Energy - Odd/Even Plan, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Energy - Natural gas, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Environmental information, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Federal Regional Council, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor - Gordon Brooks, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor - Press releases, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor's Commission on Consumer Education, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor - C. Lowrance, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor - B. Miller, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor's Commission on Employing the Handicapped, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor - Speeches, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor's Management Study Commission, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Governor's Manpower Service Council, 1975. (Box 12)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Health, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Higher Education, Council of, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Historical Landmarks Commission, Virginia, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Holton Years - A Summing Up (1970-1974), 1975. (Box 13)
  - Housing Authority, Virginia, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Housing, Office of, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1975. (Box 13)
  - Institue of Marine Science, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Justice and Crime, Division of, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Land Use, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Legislation, 1975. (Box 13)
  - Legislators, U.S., 1975. (Box 13)
  - Agriculture and Commerce, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Appropriations requests, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission (ARC), 1976. (Box 14)
  - Art Commission, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Attorney General, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Atlantic Rural Exposition - State Fair Exhibit Committee, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Bicentennial projects, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Blood Assurance Program, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Budget, 1976. (Box 14)
  - Budget, 1976. (Box 15)
  - Budget - 27T forms, 1976. (Box 15)
  - Budget - Forms, 1976. (Box 15)
  - Budget - Corrections, 1976. (Box 15)
  - Central Accounting, 1976. (Box 15)
  - Central Garage Car Pool, 1976. (Box 15)
  - Community College, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Community Action Program, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Comptroller, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Consultant firms, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Consolidated Labs, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Corrections, Dept. of (#1), 1976. (Box 16)
  - Corrections, Dept. of (#2), 1976. (Box 16)
  - Corrections, Dept. of - Air Force base, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Council of State Governments, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Crime Commission, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Economic Development Act, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Economic Opportunity Act, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Education Assistance Authority, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Education Commission of the States, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Emergency Services, Office of, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Energy, State Office of, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Energy - Cheatham Annex, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Energy Conservation Ad Hoc Committee, 1976. (Box 16)
  - Engineering and Buildings, Div. of, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Environment, Council on the, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Equal Opportunity Employment, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Federal Regulations Council, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Office, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Office - Press releases, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Office - Speeches, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Office - A. Gordon Brooks, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Office - Bruce Miller, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Office - Martha Pritchard, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Employee Advisory Comission, 1974-1975. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Manpower Services Council, 1976. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Year End Statement, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Governmental Management Study Commission, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Hampton Roads Energy Co., 1976. (Box 18)
  - Health, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, U.S. Dept. of, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Higher Education, Council of, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Housing, Office of, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Housing and Urban Development, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Housing Development Authority, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Industrial Development Authority, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Institute of Marine Science, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Division of, 1976. (Box 18)
  - Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Labor Dept., U.S., 1976. (Box 19)
  - Laundry - MCV/VCU, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Legislators - Federal, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Legislators - State, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Legislation - State, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Tracking System, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Liaison, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Minority Business Enterprise, Office of, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Virginia, 1976. (Box 19)
  - National Governors' Conference, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Offender Aid and Restoration, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Office of Management and Budget, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Outdoor Recreation, Commission of, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Police, Virginia State, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Port Authority, Virginia, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Professional and Occupational Regulation, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Property and Records, Div. of, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Public School Authority, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Probation and Parole Board, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Public Buildings Commission, Virginia, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Purchases and Supply, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Register Commission, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Revenue Sharing Program, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth - Appointments, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Southern Governor's Association, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1976. (Box 20)
  - Spurlock, J. B., 1976. (Box 21)
  - Special Programs, Office of, 1976. (Box 21)
  - S.S. United States, 1976. (Box 21)
  - State Board of Elections, 1976. (Box 21)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1976. (Box 21)
  - State Stationary (Official), 1976. (Box 21)
  - State Employees Credit Union, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Sum Sufficient Appropriation Statement - Quarterly Reports, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Telecommunications Council, Virginia Public, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Treasury, Virginia Dept. of the, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Treasury, U.S. Dept. of the, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Volunteerism, Office of, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Welfare, Dept. of, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Water Control Board, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Secretary of Education, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Secretary of Public Safety, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Secretary of Transportation, 1976. (Box 21)
  - Management Information Systems - Systems Development Standards (v. I and II), 1977. (Box 22)
  - Management Information Systems - Systems Development Standards (v. I and II), 1977. (Box 23)
  - Aircraft - State Owned, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Appropriations - Reductions, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Art Commission, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Atlantic Rural Exposition - State Fair Exhibition Committee, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Attorney General, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Biographical sketches, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Bonds - General obligation, 1977. (Box 24)
  - Budget 1978-1980 Biennium (Dept. of Planning and Budget), 1977. (Box 24)
  - Budget 1978-1980 Biennium (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Budget targeting, 1977. (Box 24)